Choose some kind of bread and a drink for tomorrow's breakfast.
Aye-aye!
Without running!
That kid doesn't listen.
Umm... for a cold, we've got water, sports drinks,
dairy products, and so on...
What's some food that's easily digestable?
Rin, do you want something for tomorrow's breakfast?
Cereal or something?
Yeah...
Daikichi...
Did I give it to her?
Rin...
Bacteria from colds is all over the place.
Some people will catch it, some won't.
But you don't have to worry about being the one who passed it on.
Can I pick something to bring her too?
Sure.
This...
Put it in the basket.
Kouki-kun!
What are you doing in the snacks aisle?!
Kouki! What about breakfast?
It came out!
ashita no koto wa wakannai
We don't know what'll happen tomorrow.
kore tte gisei to wa chigau
This feels different from a sacrifice.
nanika ga chigau
Something feels different.
batsu ge-mu ja nante omowanai
I'm not thinking of it as a punishment game.
de nande na no ka wa wakannai
I still don't know why.
chotto shakuzen to shinai kedo
Even though I don't quite feel satisfied with that,
kimi no sonzai ima daiji da nante mon ja nai
there's no question that you're important to me now.
owaranai koto nante kono yo no doko ni mo nai
There's nothing in this world that's endless.
naku no wa tsurain ja nai no
Isn't it painful having to cry?
ai no Sweet Drops, Sweet Drops
Love's sweet drops, sweet drops.
zutto yume mite itai ne
Don't you want to keep dreaming forever?
motto yasashiku shitai ne
Don't you want to be kinder?
kimi to iraretara Happy
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy.
onna no ko tte tsuyoi ne
Don't you think girls can be strong?
dakedo tokidoki yowai ne
Even though we can be weak sometimes.
bokura no negai wa Happy Happy Happy
Our wish is for happy, happy, happy.
sonna hibi mo Happy
Those days can also be happy.
Just wanna make you happy
Just wanna make you happy.
My place is here!
Yeah, we're going to go home.
I don't want your mom fussing over us.
Okay.
Here. There's food in there, so give it to your mom.
It's heavy.
It's really heavy...
Well, let's go, Rin.
Mom! Daikichi gave us food!
Listen when somebody's talking to you!
Kouki, you don't have to...
Daikichi-san...
I'm sorry you're always having to look after him...
O-Oh, no, I owe you for taking care of Rin...
How is Rin-chan?
She's a lot better now.
She went back to school today. Right?
Hello...
Hello. I'm glad you're feeling better, Rin-chan.
Yeah.
I'm making that rice gruel right now.
I'll be better soon, too.
Yep.
Rin, let's go throw my tooth!
This way!
Kouki, be careful.
All right!
Nitani-san, you may have caught your cold while taking care of Rin...
I'm sorry.
We're going to throw it from here!
I meet a lot of people every day.
It's so high up...
I go to the office by train, which is always packed.
I'm going to throw it on that roof.
There's no way to know who I caught it from.
So don't worry about it.
It's just a cold.
Okay.
Well, at least let me help with Kouki.
Even if it's just picking him up from day care...
Thank you.
Rin, we're going home.
Daikichi, let's play video games!
Sure. Next time.
Kouki, make sure to help your mom out.
Okay.
Oh, that's right.
The pudding and little drink are from Rin.
Thank you, Rin-chan!
Pudding is my favorite!
Good night.
Daikichi, hurry up!
You're up early... It's Sunday!
I told you I'm going to practice for the jump rope contest!
What's wrong?
This one's wobbly too...
Brush slowly.
Okay...
Don't mess with it!
Oww!
Please don't overdo it too soon.
Oh, I'm fine now.
I'm sorry to always be taking advantage of your generosity.
I think it's the other way around.
Really, thank you.
Not at all.
I'm surprised at Kouki...
For some reason, he just can't get that.
Kouki, you're jumping too soon.
When the jump rope swings around, you jump here, right?
Yeah.
Then you can't move your arms and legs at the same time.
I see...
Your arms go first, then your legs.
Try it once slowly.
Got it!
Daikichi! Me too! Me too!
Okay, okay. Rin, your problem is you swing your arms in too big circles.
Keep your arms in close like this...
Daikichi-san!
You're early, huh?
Good morning!
Too much energy this early in the morning...
Nobu-kun is good at it.
It's because he's got a big brother.
He'll imitate everything the older one does.
Huh...
Aren't you going to do it, Sayaka-chan?
This time, she lost one of her upper teeth...
Girls have it rough, even when they're little kids...
Sayaka-chan, what kind of container are you using to hold your teeth?
Did your parents buy you a cute one?
What's that?
You don't know about the cases people use
to hold their kids' baby teeth as a keepsake?
Keepsake?
They have these cute tiny ones.
Tiny!
Cute!
Right?
Yeah! Mine is a butterfly!
I bought one for Kouki, but...
I bet Rin would love that!
We're saving the kids' teeth, too.
I'm such an idiot! I had no idea they had those things!
It's been like this ever since I met Rin.
Fretting and getting nervous over the littlest things...
Kaga Rin
Daikichi
The meat and potato stew Daikichi
makes is really delicious. Also, Daikichi
can run very fast.
Daikichi, this is for you.
I drew it at school.
Daikichi
The meat and potato stew Daikichi
makes is really delicious. Also, Daikichi
can run very fast.
I had to write about someone at home.
Ah, well...
It's so cute!
What is this?
You put your baby teeth in there when they come out.
It's like a keepsake.
A keepsake!
Thank you, Kouki-kun's mother!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
But isn't that Kouki's?
It's okay, it's okay...
I throw my teeth!
...as you can see.
Until now, I've thrown all my teeth onto the roof.
Is that okay?
That's fine, that's fine.
Throwing them or keeping them, either way works.
I see.
Rin! I'm going to do my best with this jump rope thing, too!
There you go, touching your tooth again...
It'll come out on its own.
No matter how you look at it, she's going to look like she got punched in the face.
As long as she doesn't smile...
There you go.
Good. Okay, let's go.
Are you getting bigger again?
Huh? You too, Daikichi-san?
I'm starting to get a spare tire...
Me too!
It's tough when you get to be our age.
Somehow, I want to stop it right away.
Daikichi-san is doing it boxer-style!
That's amazing!
It's easier on the knees this way.
Huh...
Daikichi! Teach me how to do that, too!
Forget about it!
What?! Only you get to look cool?!
First, learn how to jump rope the normal way!
What was that?!
Get back here!
Me too! Me too!
Rin-chan, you're so good at doing it backwards!
Wow, kids are incredible...
Really?
They have energy to burn, don't they?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I don't know where they get it from...
One more time!
Although, adults are incredible, too...
Adults?
I think you two already know this, but I'm not Rin's dad.
We've only been living together for about a year now.
Until then, I used all my time for myself,
but once I started living with Rin, my lifestyle suddenly changed.
You guys, though, you've been with your kids ever since they were born...
For me, it's still early days, so it's nothing, really,
but I've been wondering whether you're okay with not having any
so-called "time for yourself"...
I'm fine...
Me too!
Me too.
Really?
Well, after all...
What? What?
Rin, come to think of it, wasn't today the jump rope contest?
Yeah...
Rin...
I screwed up...
How many?
15 times.
That's awful!
What about backward-style jumping?
203 times.
You can jump like that?!
Did you get first place for that?
Yeah.
Here's my certificate.
Certificate of Merit
1st year division
1st place, backwards-style jumping rope
Kaga Rin
You really did your best. This is fantastic.
But I know I could've done better with regular-style jumping rope...
Well, they only gave you one chance...
Yeah...
Anyway, you certainly learned to jump rope a lot.
I know so, at least.
Right.
I lost weight!
Huh?
Cut it out!
Are we almost there?
Maybe 10 more minutes...
They'll want to see those wobbly front teeth.
Right!
How many times do I have to tell you? Don't touch them if you can help it!
And I'll show them how I can jump rope, too!
Of course.
I bet my mom and dad will be surprised
to see how you've shot up since the last time.
I wonder if I'm taller than Auntie now.
I don't think you're that tall yet.
I'll have to tell Grandpa, too.
We're back!
Oh, Rin-chan! I've been waiting for you!
I'm home.
Look how big you've gotten!
Are you one of the taller kids in your class?
Yeah!
If you'd called, I would've picked you up at the station!
Rin can walk 10 minutes!
Soon, you'll be taller than me!
Kazumi!
Yo. You're here early.
Yeah, I just got here a little while ago.
Those clothes...
You used to wear them, right?
Yeah...
Auntie sent them to me!
Rin-chan, show me your teeth.
Okay!
Two of them in front are wobbly...
Are you okay? It doesn't hurt?
Sometimes it hurts, but I'm used to it.
I'm a pro, see?
Say, Daikichi!
Isn't there anything you can do for her?!
Her gums are turning red!
Just a little bit...
And come to think of it, when I was a kid,
you talked about pulling my loose teeth out with a thread!
A thread?!
Oh, my goodness! Did I?!
I tried to make everything soft.
Thank you!
Wanna have some freeze-dried tofu?
Yeah!
I'll have boiled beans too, Auntie!
Sure!
Eat up!
I like freeze-dried tofu!
Did one come out?
Rin-chan?
It came out!
Blood! Blood!
Mom! Tissue! Tissue!
Hold on! Hold on!
I'm fine!
Rin, use this for now!
That's a dust cloth!
Rin-chan has changed a lot.
I don't know...
This might just be the real Rin...
Huh...
So, you're getting married?
Mom was saying...
Yeah.
Good for you. She said he seemed like a nice guy.
Yeah, well...
The only thing I don't agree with is that he wants to have a kid right away.
That's a good thing, isn't it?
Are you kidding me?!
I wouldn't be able to go out drinking or go to concerts
or go on trips or eat delicious food...
I wouldn't be able to do anything anymore!
Well, you have to talk to your husband about that.
I wouldn't know...
I'm not into kids in the first place!
And I don't want to become one of those pushy moms either!
I'm not sure I could sacrifice myself to raise a kid...
Ah, I think you'd manage somehow.
If you put your mind to it...
Sometimes you just have to manage...
Easy for you to say, big brother...
Yeah, maybe...
What's that?
I've never become a father or husband, let alone a mother.
It's burning...
Yeah.
True, I don't have time to shop at my leisure,
or chat with friends over coffee.
But my time at work is my own time...
My time with my son is also my own time...
Precious time...
Other parents might look like it,
but I don't think they're doing anything special.
If you look around you, you'll see many mothers and fathers like that.
I see...
Right...
Grandpa, you know what?
Some of my adult teeth are coming in.
Hey! Rin!
Th-This is sweat!
Daikichi!
Hurry up!
Say "cheese"!
Tasu Elementary School
Entrance Ceremony
That jar...
Masako-san had it, too...
I'll be right back!
Daikichi!
What?! The other one's coming loose?!
Mirror! Mirror!
I bet I'll still keep getting nervous and worked up
over minor stuff from here on out.
I suppose it's the same way with those two.
Does it hurt?
Rin!
Daikichi, look at this!
What the heck? It's like you've got a cat's face!
I know, right?
Send a text to your parents' house!
You mean a photo?
Even so, it seems like that smile will be my happiness from now on.
Yeah!
Hurry up!
Okay, open your mouth.
And I suppose there's nothing wrong with that.
nichiyou no hareta hirusagari
It's a sunny Sunday, early in the afternoon.
kyou wa doko e yukou?
Where should we go today?
kayoi nareta itsumo no michi ga
This path I've grown so used to taking
mabushiku kagayaite mieru
seems to be shining brightly,
terasu atatakai taiyou to
as long as the warm sun is shining
tonari ni kimi ga ireba
and you are here beside me.
mou High High High
I'm already high, high, high.
hashagidasu kimochi ni
I feel like frolicking about.
utae Life Life Life
Let's sing, life, life, life.
koe wa dokomademo
Our voices can go anywhere.
mou High High High
I'm already high, high, high.
maiagaru kaze ni nori
I'm riding on the rising wind.
utae Life Life Life
Let's sing, life, life, life.
koe mo tobihaneru
Even our voices will be bouncing.
Daikichi!!